Earl 我发现你还活着呢
Earl, I noticed you're still alive.
有什么秘诀吗?
What's your secret?
嗯 其实这要归功于我积极的生活态度
Well, it's my positive attitude,
一点好基因
a little bit of genetics,
还有懂得如何照顾自己的身体
and knowing how to take care of your body.
我用荷荷葩
I use jojoba.
那是啥玩意儿 类似于乳液?
What is that, like a lotion?
不 其实是一个叫荷葩的小姐
No, it's a ho named hoba.
她每个礼拜来一次
She comes over once a week.
Max 有人给你快递了个包裹到家里
Max, you just got box delivered at home.
我可不想要什么大包裹了
I don't want another box.
这个已经够我受的了
I got my hands full with this one.
以前我家里一天到晚收快递
I used to have so many packages delivered to my house,
我爸为了省钱把把联邦快递都给买了下来
My dad had to buy Fedex just to save money.
我记得在邮件被发明之前
I remember a time before mail.
你什么都拿不到
You just didn't get stuff.
不 我不要
Nope. I don't want that.
这是我妈给的
It's a delivery from my mother.
我妈只给过我生命
The last thing she delivered was me,
让我到现在还在收拾这烂摊子
and I'm still cleaning up that mess.
你难道不好奇她给你送了什么吗?
Aren't you at least curious what she sent?
除非这是一个崭新的童年
Unless it's a brand new childhood,
我不感兴趣
I'm not interested.
Earl 拿着Max的"大包裹"吧
Here, Earl, hold Max's box.
我可是把她像女儿那样对待啊
But she's like a daughter to me.
Caroline 你看 我把我的鱼缸带来了
Look, Caroline, I brought in my fish tank,
Max说它是我的奥林匹克规格的游泳池
Which Max has been calling my Olympic-size swimming pool.
Han 看到了吧 海平面上的世界大不一样
See, Han? The world's different above sea-level.
过来 打个招呼
Now, come over here and say hello.
我现在要跟小鱼打招呼?
I'm saying hello to fish now?
我已经沦落到这地步了?
That's where I'm at?
你也是 Max
You too, Max.
我想让我的餐馆见人来见见我的小鱼家人
I want my diner family to meet my fish family.
我有个阿姨水喝得跟鱼一样多
I got an aunt that drinks like a fish.
也许她就在这里面
Maybe she's in there.
才不会 她因为开车撞死人进了监狱
Oh, no, she's in jail for vehicular manslaughter.
来享受一下我的爱的生态系统吧
Please enjoy my ecosystem of love.
不要敲玻璃!
Never tap on the glass!
看看你那肉嘟嘟的爪子
Just look at that meaty paw of yours.
这对它们还说就像是地震
It's like an earthquake to them.
哦 这是我的奖品
Oh, there's my prize.
这条是皇家蓝吊鱼
The royal blue tang fish.
五百美元
$500.
Han 你去找人给你吹箫我并不意外
Han, I'm not surprised you have to pay for blue tang,
但五百美元似乎太贵了
but $500 seems high.
嘿 Han 我那个小姐只要25美元
Hey Han, jojoba'll do it for 25.
好吧 我希望你的鱼在这里能过得开心
Well, I hope your fish will be very happy here.
其他人在这都不开心 不过谁知道这鱼呢
I mean, no one else is, but who knows.
我们走 Max
Let's go, Max.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫
时间轴: Pisces夜
翻译: 黄字君  纯洁沫  黄阿姨  Morning
校对: 桃茜茜
Oleg把连姆·尼森的女儿给绑架了吗
Did Oleg take Liam Neeson's daughter?
我正在和全部女朋友分手呢
I'm breaking up with all my ladies
这样我才能和Sophie重新开始
so I can start up again with Sophie.
可是这个Oksana不肯屈服
And Oksana's not taking it lying down,
或是像她从前那样俯低身子
or bent over like she usually is.
好吧 可惜我没见到她
Well, I'm sorry I never got to meet her.
就告诉她你和Sophie已经决定...
Just tell her that you and Sophie have decided to be...
在乌克兰语里"一夫一妻制"怎么说?
What's the Ukrainian word for "monogamy"?
没这个词
There isn't one.
你要么丑得没人要 要么睡遍天下
You're either ugly or you're sleeping with everyone.
绝对不行 不行
Uh-uh. No way.
把它留在外面
Leave it out here.
让拆弹部队去处理它
Let the bomb-squad figure it out.
你难道不想知道她送你了什么吗?
Don't you wanna know what she sent you?
可能那里面有钱
Maybe there's money in there.
所以你就打算把它留在走道上
So you're just gonna leave it out in the hall
就像留给客房服务处理的垃圾?
like a room service tray?
哦 天啊 我曾经有客房服务
Oh, my god, I used to have room service.
哦 天啊 我曾经有自己的房间
Oh, my god, I used to have a room.
好吧 我可不希望它在我公寓里
Well, I don't want it in the apartment.
这是一个充满正能量的地方
This is a place of positive energy and good vibes.
我明天把它送回去
I'm sending it back to her tomorrow.
直到我被随便埋葬的那一天
I will go to my shallow, unmarked grave
我都不要知道这包裹里有什么
not knowing what's in that box.
嘿 Max 你门外有个箱子
Hey, Max, you got a box out here,
里面还有只小熊呢!
and there's a bear in it!
哦 天啊
Oh, my god.
她还留着那个?
She kept that?
我妈怎么还留着那个?
How did my mom ever keep that?
她连她的牙齿都保不住
She can't even keep her teeth.
箱子里就这个?
That's what was in the box?
一个泰迪熊玩偶?
A teddy ruxpin doll?
你在发霉熊网注册了?
Are you registered at mustybears.com?
这不是一个玩偶 他有自己名字的
Not a doll and not his name.
我把它的名字正式改为T-rux
I had it legally changed T-rux.
我用的是我妈的那个律师
I used the same lawyer my mom hired
他说只要我宣称是印第安人
to declare me native american so she didn't have to pay
那么她就不用付赌场的停车费
for parking at the casino.
六个月来 我接电话时都得称自己为
For six months, I had to answer the phone,
麦克斯·光荣脚
"Max Proudfoot."
你知道吗 在波兰 我们没有玩偶
You know, in Poland, we didn't have dolls.
我们就雇佣一些吉普赛孩子
Yeah, we just hired little gypsy kids
然后带着他们到处跑
and we carried them around.
对了c  我的那个叫Gurgio
Yeah, mine was called Gurgio.
而且 我觉得他有小儿麻痹症
Yeah, and I think uh, he had a little bit of polio.
嘿 这种东西不会说话吗?
Hey, didn't those things talk?
如果给它装上四个栅偏压电池就会说话了
They did if you had four "c" batteries.
等等 我觉得我好像有这号电池
Wait, I think I have some.
是的 这只可爱的泰迪熊
Yup, they came with this adorable teddy bear
本身自带有会唱歌的磁盘
singing cassette, so of course,
不过我把它砸了 然后自己给安装了一个
I smashed that with a rock and made my own.
我的Gurgio不会说话
Yeah, my Gurgio didn't talk.
我都不知道他有没有舌头
I'm not sure he had a tongue.
但他总是紧紧地抓着我
But he used to squeeze me really tight.
后来我发现 他已经35岁了
And then I found out later, he was 35.
你床头柜里有四个栅偏压电池?
You had four "c" batteries in your nightstand?
从啥玩意抠出来的啊
From what?
你到底想不想听这只熊说话
Do you wanna hear the bear talk or don't you?
哦 女孩们 对不起啦
Oh, I'm sorry, girls.
我得接这个电话
I gotta take this.
这是另一个我要分手的男人
It's another guy that I'm breaking it off with.
我希望Oleg值得我这么做
I sure hope Oleg's worth it.
我刚刚甩了一个多重人格的男人
I just dumped a guy with multiple personalities.
于是他的三个反应是 没问题
Yeah, and he took it okay,
不太好
and not great,
以及很伤心
and pretty bad.
里面连张纸条也没有
There's no note or anything.
这就是个让人失望的包裹
This box is really just a well of disappointment.
你妈妈为啥要寄这个给你?
Why would your mother send you this?
她做事哪有为啥?
Why would she do anything?
你说她为啥咬我家的狗?
Why would she bite our dog?
还和我家的南瓜灯亲热?
Why would she make out with our jack o'lantern?
我哪知道
I don't know.
Max 在这么多年之后 她把你最爱的
Well, Max, she did send you your favorite toy
玩具寄给了你
after all these years.
说不定她想做出补偿呢
Maybe she's trying to make amends.
做出补偿?
Oh, make amends?
她连个三明治也做不出来
She couldn't even make me a sandwich.
准备好了?
Okay, you ready?
我知道你是 但我呢?
I know you are, but what am I?
哦 天啊 Max 那是你吗?
Oh, my god. Max, is that you?
那是小Max的声音吗?
Is that your little Max voice?
小心点 我准备放臭屁啦
Careful, I'm about to open up a can of whoop ass.
就是你! 那时你几岁了?
It is you! How old were you there?
十岁 "臭屁"是我那会儿的口头禅
Ten. "whoop ass" was kind of my thing.
现在也是
Still is.
我当然知道你也有童年
I mean, I guess I always knew you were a little kid once,
但直到听到你的声音我才想象得到
But I couldn't picture it till I heard that.
就好比我从来想象不到自己
Like I couldn't picture me eating fruit
有一天会从加油站拿水果吃一样
From an Exxon station till I did that.
你们准备好点单了吗?
So, are you two ready to order?
嗯 我要火鸡三明治配薯条
Oh, yeah. I'll have the turkey club with fries.
这就是你没人要的原因 Rita
This is why you're single, Rita.
我有人要的 我嫁给你爸爸了
I'm not single. I'm married to your father.
我爱你 但不要把你的生活方式强灌给我
I love you, but stop pushing your lifestyle in my face.
我要一份沙拉 配上蘸酱
I'll have the salad. Dressing on the side.
显然的么
Obvs.
显然的啦 显然
Obvs, obvs.
我要把T-rux寄回给我妈
Well, I'm sending T-rux back to my mother.
我在Han办公室里找到的空箱子
He's going right into this empty box
正好装得下它
I found in Han's office.
Max 你寄回去之前
And Max, before you send it back,
先把电池还给我
I'm gonna need those batteries.
哦 别担心 我没兴趣看你
Oh, don't worry, I have no desire to see you
和震动奶昔机玩抱抱
hugging the milkshake machine.
哦... 我的... 天啊!
Oh... my... god!
那只是华斯比泰迪熊吗?
Is that a teddy ruxpin doll?
Rita 我想要!
Rita, I want that!
你刚过完生日 Elliot
Your birthday just passed, Elliot.
可我的出柜派对就快到了
But my coming out party is coming up.
那是什么 女孩成人礼之类的?
What is that, like a queen-ceanera?
真婊 我喜欢她
So bitchy. Love her.
一只旧华斯比泰迪熊差不多值500美元
A vintage teddy ruxpin is worth like, $500,
我妈妈有工作 所以她得花钱买我的爱
And my mom works, so she has to buy my love.
再多嘴 我就取消你的水疗日
One more word, and I'm taking away spa day.
真残酷 亲爱的
That's harsh, honey.
他对90年代特别着迷
He's obsessed with the '90s.
那会儿你还没出生呢
But you weren't even born.
我知道 都怪她
I know. I blame her.
直到人老珠黄才找到男人
She couldn't find a man till late in life.
美甲也取消掉了
There go the pedicures.
凉鞋穿不了咯
There go my sandals.
虽然我挺喜欢看真人版"威尔和格蕾丝"
As much as I love watching Will and Grace,
"威尔和格蕾丝", 1998年美剧, 其中男主角为同性恋, 女主角为异性恋
但这只熊不卖
this guy's not for sale.
我得把它寄回我妈妈那儿
I'm sending him back to my mother's place,
根据罗德岛假释处的记录
which, according to the Rhode Island parole office,
位于必乐透杂货店外面的一个纸板房
is a cardboard shanty town outside of big lots.
这是我的名片
Well, here's my card.
面对现实吧 你看着就像是及需五百美元
And let's face it, you look like you could use $500.
真婊 我喜欢他!
So bitchy. Love him!
刚刚一个幼版的基佬安德森·库珀
I was just offered $500 for T-rux
想用500美元买我的T-rux
from baby anderson cooper.
他还有名片?
He has cards?
我居然嫉妒一个九岁的孩子?
I'm jealous of a nine-year-old?
我都沦落到啥地步了?
That's where I'm at?
嘿 虽然我很想要这500美元
Hey, as much as I would like that $500,
可我绝不能让我妈妈以为
my mother doesn't get to think this bear
靠一只熊就能弥补我的童年
gets to make up for my childhood.
才不能这么便宜了她
She doesn't get off that easy.
相信我 我们俩曾经在一张沙发上睡了9个月
Trust me, we shared a pullout couch for nine months.
姑娘们 能过来一下吗?
Girls, can I see you over here?
简直不敢相信我又要去和鱼说话了
I can't believe we have to talk to the fish again.
简直不敢相信Max竟然还没把Han按进鱼缸里
I can't believe Max hasn't put Han in the tank yet.
Max和Caroline 今天开始每个晚上
Max, Caroline, every night from now on,
我都要你们用网兜清扫水面
I need you to move the skimmer along the top of the water
撇取漂浮物
and take out the floating matter.
Han 自从被迫清扫老人用过的便池后
Han, you know I'm off diner poop patrol for life
我就再也不干餐厅粪便清扫员的活了吧
after I had to clean the booth where the senior left...
打扫那种像烂透了的桨果
Well, we'll just call it an elderberry.
好吧 Caroline Max不肯 所以归你了
Well, Caroline, Max said no, so you have to do it.
Han 一走到鱼缸边你就成了大佬
Han, you're kind of a baller around your fish.
好吧 我速战速决
All right, I'm gonna do this fast.
冲进去冲出来...
Get in and get out...
就和上次浴室里有鸟一样
Same thing I do when that bird is in our shower.
拿一下 Max
Pick up, Max.
我打来是想告诉你 我和别人一起了
Look, I'm calling to tell you I met somebody else
所以我和你分手了
so I'm breaking up with you.
现在把电话给你妈妈 我和她也要分手
Now put your mother on. I'm breaking up with her too.
简直不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我现在成了鱼的海滨服务生
I'm a cabana boy for fish.
这回我能在简历的"最高法院实习生"下面
I guess now I can add "fish poop remover"
加上"鱼粪清洁工"这一条了
to my resume next to "supreme court intern."
最后那一下好像舀出了一条鱼
I feel like there was a fish in that last one.
没错
Yup.
哦 天啊 是贵的那条!
Oh, no, it's the expensive one!
真是我的一贯风格
That's so me.
我真没想到能在你30岁前
I really didn't expect to see you digging through garbage
看到你翻垃圾
till you were 30.
哦! 啊! 它还活着!
Oh! Ah! Ugh! It's still alive!
我得让它保持湿润
I need to keep her wet.
哦 被金枪鱼糊了一身 肯定得有皮肉伤了
Oh, covered in tuna, that's gotta be traumatic for it.
我感觉它好像滑下下水道了
I feel like it went down the drain.
这是个意外 我发誓
It was an accident. I swear.
我喜欢鱼 我绝不会伤害它们
I love fish. I would never hurt one.
除非你算上吃寿司 因为我会吃得
Unless you count eating sushi, 'cause then I'm like
比开膛手杰克杀人还凶残
Jack the Ripper.
Caroline 一切都还好吗?
Caroline, are things going swimmingly?
杰克 他在和你说话呢
Jack, he's talking to you.
呃  哦 是的 一切都好
Uh, oh, yeah. Swimmingly.
特别是蓝色那条
Especially the blue one.
它躲进自己的小房子里了
He went in his little house.
它不想让其他小伙伴
He doesn't like to use the restroom
看到它在上厕所
In front of his friends.
是啊 我和它很有共同点的
Yeah, we're a lot alike.
谢谢您这么快接见我们
Thank you so much for seeing us so quickly.
没事 你们先在这等着
Sure, you guys can just wait in here.
Elliot正在做普拉提 快结束了
Elliot's finishing up with his pilates.
给你们提个醒
Do yourselves a favor.
记得赞他的核心肌群相当紧实
Tell him his core looks tight.
马克思 对不起 害你要卖掉T-rux小熊
Max, I'm so sorry you have to sell T-rux
帮我凑钱买鱼
For the fish money because of me.
生气中 直接看拳吧
Talked to the fist, because the face is pissed.
连熊都敢给我脸色?
I'm getting attitude from a bear?
我已经沦落到这种地步了?
That's where I'm at?
他有这么多90年代的东西 太神奇了
I can't believe all this stuff he has from the '90s.
他出柜都要开派对 我也是醉了
I can't believe he has to have a party to come out.
这娃先出生 再出柜
That kid came out, out.
我猜他连脐带都是古驰的
His umbilical cord is a gucci belt
哦... 看看这些玩具!
Oh...t hese toys!
跟我小时候一样样的
This is like looking back at my childhood
不过你懂得 我那时候彩虹还没什么政治意义
But, you know, a time before rainbows became political.
天啊 天啊
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
哦 老天
Oh, my god.
一个真人比例的芭比!
A my size barbie!
我曾经坐拥十个
I had ten of these.
不是拿来玩 是以防遇到绑架之际
Not to play with, they were used as decoys
可以用它们来当替身 迷惑坏人
In case of a hostage situation.
现在你已经被人生绑架了
And now your whole life's a hostage situation.
对不起 来迟了
Sorry I'm late.
我和我的教练Gary聊
My trainer, Gary, and I got derailed
聊橘郡男孩里的贵妇的真实生活
Talking about the real housewives of Orange County.
你的核心肌群看起来好紧实
Your core looks really good.
我知道 亲
I know, honey.
我先找我的支票本 你们跟奥尔森姐妹说说话
Now while I get my check book, say hello to the Olsens.
你玩具真多
You got a lot of toys.
我在与你相仿的年纪之时 只有这个
When I was a girl your age, I only had this.
我可不可以和真人芭比玩
I don't suppose I could play with my size barbie
那么一下下
For a second.
你的脸上写着"不行 贱人"
I feel like that's a "no, bitch."
不... 不只是玩具
I'm not... I'm not just talking about the toys.
整个房间的布置都很漂亮
You got a pretty sweet set-up.
你想要什么 外面的那个好心阿姨都会给你
That nice lady out there, giving you everything you want,
照顾你
Taking care of you.
就是个妈妈 大家都有
She's just a mom. Everyone has one.
也不一定 有人只有超酷的小熊
Not really. Some people just have bad ass bears.
Max 你确定吗?
Max, are you sure about this?
这是你童年的唯一纪念
This is the only thing you have from your childhood.
错 我头上还有个坑 圆头锤敲的
Not true, I have a dent in my skull
也是童年纪念
From a ball-peen hammer.
自此我再也不敢在观看
The last time I change the channel
"三人行"的时候换台了
During Three's company.
我们动作快点好吗?
Can we fast forward this to me having the bear
把熊卖给我 你们就可以走了
And you two leaving?
好的 拿去吧 没关系
Okay, just take it, it doesn't matter.
不行 Max 怎么会没关系
No, Max. It does matter.
这熊不能卖
We're not selling this.
他的玩具够多了
He has enough toys.
我是说 人家好像摸摸那个真人芭比
I mean, all I wanted to do was touch the life-size barbie.
好的 我知道现在是个什么节奏了
Okay, I see what's happening.
我买豆豆娃娃的时候也遇到过这种情况
I've been down this road with the beanie babies.
我出六百块
I'll give you 600 for the bear.
卖了
Sold.
不可以 Max! 那熊是你的童年啊
No, max! That's your childhood.
- 七百  - 成交!
- 700.  - Sold!
不行 Max！
No, Max!
Caroline 我的童年不值七百
Caroline, my childhood is not worth $700.
我妈妈最多给过我四十块
The most my mother ever got for me was 40 bucks
加上一个能量杯
And a big gulp.
但是熊里面住着一个小小的你啊 Max
But that's "little you" in there, Max.
她是无价的
And she's priceless.
这小姑娘绝对会把声音洗掉
And she's about to erased and taped over
用来录冰雪奇缘的原声
by the soundtrack from frozen.
冰雪奇缘?
Frozen?
你当我谁啊? 去年的我吗?
Who am I? Me, a year ago?
不行 不卖
No. Can't have her.
好吧 那另外一个孩子要怎么应付?
Well, what are we gonna do now about the other child?
餐馆里那个老小孩
The one in the diner?
我想他也该长大了
Well, I guess he's just gonna have to grow up.
长大? 你觉得 他要是有那能力
Grow up? You think if he had that ability,
会留着不用吗?
He wouldn't have used it yet?
所以... 熊不卖了?
So what... No bear?
拜托 你会遇到自己生命中的"熊抱"
Oh, please! You'll have a bear in your life.
信姐没错
Trust me.
好吧 Max
All right, Max.
你会帮我告诉他 是不是?
You're gonna help me tell him, right?
你喜欢告诉他坏消息
You like giving him bad news.
不 我只喜欢告诉他短小
No, I like giving him bad news about how he's short
头又大的坏消息
and has a big head.
你懂的 那种好笑的坏消息
You know, fun bad news.
我要宣布一个振奋人心的消息!
Exciting news!
我给鱼鱼买了房房
I got the fishies a new house!
是丧失赎回权的抵押品 好便宜的
I got it cheap. It was a foreclosure.
嗯 Han 你能过来吗 我跟你说句话
Uh, Han, can we talk to you over there
去卡座说... 最远的那个?
In the booth... The far booth?
可以稍等吗? 我要把房子放到鱼鱼的公寓里
Can it wait? I want to put in the new condo
这样Max就不会管我叫恶房东了
So Max will stop calling me a slum lord.
哦 这个不急啊
Oh, that can wait, I mean, those fish
这些鱼又不会到处乱跑
Aren't going anywhere.
除了那只蓝色的 它绝对
Except for the blue one, who's definitely playing
是在玩什么诡异的躲猫猫游戏
Some kind of twisted game of hide and seek.
是啊 它超爱那个小房子的
Oh, yeah, he loves that little house.
那这个它一定会更喜欢
He's going to love this one even more.
Max 你可以过来陪我吗?
Max, can you join me?
人家在端盘子 好忙的
I'm pretty busy waiting on tables right now.
好了 现在是什么情况?
Okay, what's going on?
Max这辈子就从来没正经端过盘子
Max has never waited on a table in her life.
Max 我需要你 快过来
Max, I need you over here.
人家正在端烤奶酪
I'm just putting down this grilled cheese
再不端 就冷了
'Cause I don't want it to get cold.
我这会儿要吓尿了!
Now I'm freaking out!
Max 不要这样对我
Max, don't do this to me.
我知道你把那些尸体都埋在哪里的 真的
I know where the bodies are buried, literally.
我每六个月都会挪一次
I move them every six months.
好了 是什么事?
Well, what is it?
Han 人的一生总会碰上一些事情
Han, sometimes in life, things happen
一些不如意的事情
That you don't want to happen.
没错
Yes.
即使很难面对 但你要知道
And even though it's hard, you know,
你还是不得不面对
You just have to face up to it.
应该是吧
I suppose.
天啊 真不容易
Oh, dear god, this is rough.
那个...
And, well...
Han 我真的不想跟你说这事
Han, I don't wanna have to tell you this,
我知道这是你最不想听到的事情...
I know this is the last thing you ever want to hear...
快说吧!
Oh, just say it!
卫生棉机器又坏了
The tampon machine is broken again.
我等会儿会戴上眼罩去把它修好
Later, I'll get my blindfold and fix it.
想听建议吗?
Word of advice?
如果你最终真的把我杀了
When you do finally kill me,
你要在警察面前摆出一副不正经的样子
You gotta work on your game face for the cops.
Max 别这样
Max, please.
我没法对Han说我弄死了他的鱼
I can't tell Han I murdered his fish.
我说不出口
I can't.
我也说不出口
Well, I can't tell him either.
别争了 我去跟他说
Oh, hell, I'll tell him.
我是个黑人 大家总会以为是我干的
I'm a black man, everyone already assumes I did it.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you so much.
这不过是条鱼 他会没事的
It's just a fish. He'll be fine.
我决定待会儿在小蓝鱼的生日派对上
I've decided I'll give blue the new house
送它一间新房子
at its birthday party later.
今天是那条鱼的生日?
It's the damn fish's birthday?
我不干了
I'm out.
你们都被邀请了
And you're all invited.
小蓝鱼今天两周岁了
Blue's two years old today.
它们通常活不了那么久
They don't usually live that long.
对 确实活不了
No, they do not.
看他这样 我们怎么说得出口
That's it, we can't tell him.
虽然我猜Han的年纪
Even at Han's age, which I am guessing
是在14到53岁之间
is somewhere between 14 and 53,
但有些孩子还没准备好长大
Some kids just aren't ready to grow up.
我们要怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
我们应该跑出去 买条新的
We're gonna run out and buy a new one.
我们去哪儿弄钱?
Where are we gonna get the money?
Oleg 你还记得两年前
Oleg, you know how two years ago
你付一千美元让我给你按背吗?
you offered me $1,000 for a back rub?
当然
Of course.
Caroline给你按背 只收五百
Caroline will do it for $500.
成交 最后的狂欢
Deal. One last hurrah.
隔着衣服 只按腰部以上
Over the clothes, above the waist,
虽然说不上理由 但你必须穿避孕套
And I don't know why, but you have to wear a condom.
没错 请找Dominic Rosello神父
Yes, father Dominic Rosello, please.
他正在庆祝弥撒?
Oh, he's celebrating mass?
好吧 你能不能告诉他Sophie Kachinski
Oh yeah, could you just tell him that Sophie Kachinski
正向一夫一妻转变?
is converting to monogamy?
她不能再跪倒他的圣坛前面了
And uh, she won't be kneeling at his altar anymore.
对 就这么说 他会明白的
Oh, yeah, yeah, he'll understand.
Han在哪儿 他知道了吗?
Where's Han and does he know?
不知道 但我没办法继续假装我还看见那条鱼
No, but I can't keep pretending I see that fish.
我有青光眼又整天抽嗨了
I'm a pot-head with a touch of glaucoma.
我看见不存在的东西
I'm seeing stuff that's not there.
却看不见存在的东西
Not seeing stuff that's there
我都糊涂了
It's confusing.
好吧 过来
Okay. Come on, come on.
放进去 放进去
Put it in, put it in, put it in.
我对每一个跟你约会过的人
I have a whole new respect for every guy
产生了新的敬意
that's ever gone out with you.
生日快乐 小蓝鱼!
Happy birthday, blue!
生日快乐 小蓝鱼
Happy birthday. Happy birthday, blue.
小蓝鱼在哪儿?
Where's blue?
我一整天都没看见它
I haven't seen her all day.
我刚刚看见了
I just saw it.
对 它肯定在那里
Yeah, it was definitely there.
难道你不给蛋糕拍个照
You're not gonna give blue that cupcake
就直接给小蓝鱼? 你的平板电脑呢?
without a photo-op, are you? Where's your ipad?
我刚刚看见了 没错 它肯定在那里
I just saw it. Yeah, it was definitely there.
是啊 Han 去拿平板!
Yeah, Han, go!
你需要拍张照 这样你就能放上脸书
You need a pic so you can post it on facebook
或者鱼书之类的
or fishbook or whatever.
好主意 给你 拿着蛋糕
Good idea. Here, hold this.
嘿 Caroline 你看起来没那么平了
Hey, Caroline, you look less flat.
你终于去做了隆胸手术了?
You finally get that boob job you needed?
我觉得是袋子破了
I feel like the baggy broke.
对 你用便宜填充物的话就会这样
Yup, that's what happens when you get the cheap implants.
天啊 真的有东西
Oh, my god, there is definitely something
在我胸罩里动
moving around in my bra.
你还认得这种感觉 也算是件好事
Well, it's good you can still recognize that feeling.
没错... 哦! 哦! 我摸到了!
It's right... Oh! Oh! I touched it!
真恶心!
Gross!
来人把手伸进我的胸罩来帮我啊
Someone, put your hand in my bra and help me.
为啥是现在? 现在我已经不干这行了!
Why now? Now that I'm off the market!
不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
我怕我会把它挤扁然后又弄死了
I'm afraid I'm gonna squish it and kill it again.
好了 直接爬上柜台 把它倒进鱼缸里
Okay, just get up on the counter and drop it in the tank.
什么?
What?
爬上柜台 打开你的腿
Get up on the counter, spread your legs,
然后让它直接掉进缸里
And just let it fall into the tank.
你知道吗?
You know what?
把擦背的事忘了 做完这个 我们就扯平了
Forget the back rub. After this, we're square.
好了 在鱼缸上叉开腿 拉起你的工作服
Okay, straddle the tank, pull out your uniform,
然后让它去吧
And let it go.
现在我欠你钱了
Now I owe you money.
直接在鱼缸上蹲下 就像你正在生
Just squat over the tank like you're delivering
一条鱼宝宝
A fish baby.
我在生鱼宝宝?
I'm delivering a fish baby?
我已经沦落到这种地步了?
This is where I'm at?
别说话了 你已经走到这地步了
Stop asking. That's where you're at.
好了 现在我确实看见了 对吗?
Okay, now that I saw, right?
Caroline 下来!
Caroline, get down!
这不是那种派对
It's not that kind of party.
Max 你真的还要把T-rux送回去?
Max, you're really still gonna send t-rux back?
在我们被一个小孩用
After we got bullied by a kid
蒂凡妮·西森的枕头欺辱之后?
with a Tiffani Amber Thiessen pillow?
别紧张 T-rux还在收银台那里
Relax, T-rux is right over there by the register.
对了 他是我们的第一个员工
And by the way, he's our first employee.
一旦我们遇到挑事儿的顾客 它就会说
Anytime we get a bone-head customer, he can say,
"看拳吧...
"talk to the fist...
因为正在生气中"
'cause the face is pissed."
我就是给我妈妈寄了一些东西
I'm just sending my mother something
感谢她在我的童年时期
to say thank you for everything she gave me
给予我的一切
when I was a child.
那里面有什么?
Aww, what's in there?
啥都没有!
Nothing!